addfreestats.com 2018-12-27

# AFS Analytics Politique de Confidentialité

AFS Analytics services is provided and developed by [DataSense Company](https://www.datasense-analytics.com/).

AFS Analytics a créé cette déclaration de confidentialité afin de démontrer son engagement au respect de la vie privée de ses membres et utilisateurs. Ce qui suit révèle les informations à propos des pratiques de ce site en ce qui concerne la diffusion et la collecte des données, or users of a website using AFS web analytics solution.

### if you are a user of a website using AFS Analytics solution

AFS Analylics wich complies with the general data protection regulations, may save personal data (as defined by the GDPR) as a subcontractor, including a unique number consisting of alphanumeric characters identifying you. This encrypted data is saved on secure servers located in France or in Canada. Canada guarantees data protection under Articles 44 and 46 of the GDPR. No banking information is transmitted to AFS Analytics. 

The owner of the AFS analytics account is sole owner of the personally identifiable or not information data collected on their website. AFS Analytics does not share, sell, or claim any rights to this data. The storage duration is defined by the AFS Analytics account owner and is limited to 365 days by default. You may request the deletion or modification of this data by contacting the Data Manager of the owner of the account. The cookies are exclusively attached to their domain name: first-party Cookies. The owner of these cookies are the owner of the website where the AFS Analytics tracking code is pasted, and you can oppose their registration. 

**AFS Analytics does not share or sell any collected information to third parties.**

AFS Analytics ne recueille pas d’informations personnelles vous concernant. Votre nom, adresse, numéro de téléphone et adresse e-mail restent votre propriété. AFS Analytics, cependant, recueille des informations spécifiques à la façon dont vous utilisez Internet. Les serveurs AFS Analytics enregistrent des informations non personnelle, tels que, mais sans s'y limiter, le serveur auquel vous êtes connecté, l'emplacement géographique, l'ISP que vous utilisez, le type de navigateur que vous utilisez, et votre adresse IP. Ces informations sont collectées uniquement à des fins statistiques. 

### Les Membres enregistrés d’ AFS Analytics

If You create an account on AFS Analytics, ou are responsible for maintaining the security of Your account and its content, and You are fully responsible for all activities that occur under the account and any other actions taken in connection with the Website. DataSense (AFS Analytics) will not be liable for any acts or omissions by You, including any damages of any kind incurred as a result of such acts or omissions. 

**Your website must be compliant with the GDPR:**  

* Ask consent to your users prior to use cookies.
* Set-up analytic.js to comply with the European law on the deposit of cookies
* Read [](https://www.afsanalytics.com/info/146/analytics-gdpr.html)GDPR Compliance and Privacy document.
* Add the [disclaimer about AFS Analytics](https://www.afsanalytics.com/info/146/analytics-gdpr.html) in your terms and condition or privacy policy. 

We may occasionally communicate with you regarding our products, services, news, and events. You have the option to not receive this information. We provide an opt-out function within all email communications of this nature or will cease to communicate with you for this purpose if you contact us and tell us not to communicate this information to you. The only kind of these communications that you may not “opt-out” of are those required to communicate announcements related to the Services, including information specific to your account, planned Services suspensions, and outages. We will attempt to minimize this type of communication to you. 

**General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR)**

_Data export_   
Some data that been stored for you on our servers can be exported to CSV directly by request sent to the support team. We guarantee the export of the data will be made within 15 business days after a request is received. This service is free for premium account, for FREE accounts, this service will be billed. 

_Data retention_  
For PREMIUM account, you can select the period of the data retention. For FREE account, all tracked data that was stored more than 180 days will be permanently deleted from our system. 

_Data Location_  
All personal data about our regisered members are encrypted and saved on secure servers located in France or in Canada. Canada guarantees data protection under Articles 44 and 46 of the GDPR. No banking information is transmitted to AFS Analytics. 

_Data collected_  
We collect information related to a platform user and our Services usage:  

* Registration information: information you provide to us when you sign up to our system.
* Profile settings: you can view and edit various preferences as well as personal details on “Profile” settings.
* Subscription plan and billing information: we store information about your subscription plan and billing information. We don't store any payment details. All payments are processed by our 3rd party partners (Stripe or Paypal). 
* Other data you want to share: We may collect your personal information or data if you submit it to us in other contexts.

**AFS Analytics does not share or sell any collected information to third parties.**  
AFS Analytics respecte totalement la confidentialité de toutes les informations personnelles recueillies auprès de ses membres inscrits. Cela inclut les données personnelles fournies pendant le processus d'inscription. 

### Rights to access, rectification or erasure, restriction and objection of processing

You have the right to access, rectification, opposition, erasure (“right to be forgotten”), and restriction of the processing your personal data by directing any of such requests to [DataSense](https://www.datasense-analytics.com/) or [AFS Analytics](https://www.afsanalytics.com/contact.html) . In order to make things easier for you, and without prejudice to the legal requirements DataSense must comply with under the laws, DataSenseO allows you to exercise the above-mentioned rights by sending an email to our data manager Christophe Jacquet from DataSense company, christophe(at)datasense.fr 

### Account deletion

All users, who want to constantly delete their accounts and all the associated data, could do it by themselves in their profile (or contact the team for premium account). All data is permanently deleted from all our servers and it couldn’t be restored. 

### Cookies

Les «cookies» sont des identifiants qu'un site web peut envoyer à votre navigateur afin de garder sur votre ordinateur des données servant à vous reconnaitre lors de vos prochaines visites. La plupart des cookies expirent par eux-mêmes après une courte période de temps. Notre site internet utilise des cookies dans le seul but de vous authentifier. Nous ne transférons aucunes données de cookie à d'autres sites.. 

Si vous ne voulez pas le bénéfice de cookies, il existe une procédure simple pour supprimer manuellement les cookies. S'il vous plaît consulter la documentation d'aide de votre navigateur Web pour plus d'informations. Toutefois en cas de suppression de Cookies, AFS Analytics risque de ne plus fonctionner correctement notamment pour les authentifications. 

### Nous contacter

Si vous avez des questions supplémentaires sur l'engagement d'AFS Analytics à propos de la vie privée de ses consommateurs, [contactez-nous](https://www.afsanalytics.com/fr/contact.html)..
